With the adjustments of the last lectures, we got leaner reducer files. Generally, we split our actions
Son derslerin ayarlamalar ile azalttmz veya azalttmzda genel olarak drcler zerindeki eylemlerimizi bir hayran
and reducers across a lot of files and created a lot of boilerplate code here. For a small project as this
kitlesi arasnda bltrdk ve kk bir proje iin burada bir hayli kullanl kod
one,
hazrladk.
this is clearly overkill but also it allows me to show you what you can do and that will become important
Bu aka acyor ama ayn zamanda size ne yapabileceinizi gstermeme izin veriyor ve daha byk
as you build bigger applications.
uygulamalar olutururken bu nem kazanacak.
We'll already see some advantages in the burger builder app which we'll work on in the next course module
Bergere Boulder uygulamasnda tekrar bir sonraki ders modlnde alacak baz
again.
avantajlar greceiz.
I wanted to highlight these possible improvements or restructurings to allow you to write as lean and
olduunca tepki verebilmen iin bu olas gelimeleri veya yeniden yaplanmalar vurgulamak istedim.
understandable reducers actions and react applications in general as possible.
Yaln ve anlalabilir redksiyon eylemcileri olarak binmeye ve uygulamalar genel olarak mmkn
Now one other thing I want to quickly dive into is an alternative folder structure,
imdi hzla dal etmek istediim baka bir ey alternatif bir klasr yaps.
now the folder structure really is something you can find styles of different approaches,
imdi klasr yaps gerekten binlerce farkl yaklam bulabileceiniz bir ey.
the approach I chose in this course is the one you'll probably see the most often in react projects,
Bu derste setiim yaklam, en sk tekrarlanan projeleri greceksiniz.
it's quite good with the containers and components differentiation and then the store.
Kaplar ve bileenler farkllamas ve daha sonra maaza ile olduka iyi.
Now as your store grows, you might add more and more action and reducer files and you'll notice that
imdi maazanz bydke giderek daha fazla eylem ekleyebilir ve azaltabilir veya debilir
some of your reducer files refer to some container and other reducer files to another container.
ve redktr dosyalarndan bazlarnn baz kaplar, Faas' baka bir kapta azalttn greceksiniz.
For that reason, in an alternative project structure, you could create a store subfolder in every container
klasr oluturabilir ve sadece indirgeyiciyi ve l olarak verilen konteyner iin eylemleri o maazaya ekleyebilirsiniz.
and then only add the reducer and the actions for that given container to that store.
Bu sebeple ve alternatif bir proje yaps iin, her konteynerde bir depo alt
And if you had more containers, each container folder had a store folder, you wouldn't have that global
Ve daha fazla konteyneriniz olsayd her konteyner klasrnde bir maaza klasr vard, bu genel
store folder and you would have a lot of actions and reducers for each container which you then still
maaza klasrnz olmazd ve her bir konteyner iin redktrlerde bir sr ilem gerekletirdikten
combine together in your index.js file though.
sonra yine de dizin caznzda Faldo'yu bir araya getirirsiniz.
So this is an alternative,
Yani bu bir alternatif.
you can also mix that with a global store for some global or shared operations you might need everywhere,
Deaderick, insanlar bulabileceiniz ve bir ok dnceyle bir sr makaleyi okuyabileceiniz bir eydir; ayrca,
that really is something you can fine tune and where you can read a lot of articles with a lot of opinions.
ihtiyacnz olabilecek baz kresel veya paylaml ilemler iin global bir maazayla birlikte kullanabilirsiniz.
Find the approach you like, for many projects,
Pek ok proje iin beendiiniz yaklam bulun.
the approach shown here with a central store folder should be fine
Burada bir merkezi maaza klasr ile gsterilen yaklam iyi olmaldr.
but be aware that you're free to deviate from that when needed.
Ancak, ihtiya duyulduunda ondan ayrlmak iin serbest olduunuzun farknda olun.